(Howard:)Yeah, right.
(Howard:)-Dr. Plimpton?
-Hi.
(Elizabeth:)-Howard, right?
-Uh, yeah.
(Elizabeth:)Can I ask you a question, Howard?
(Elizabeth:)Do you like role-playing games?
Yeah, sure. Heh.
(Howard:)In fact, I'm a dungeon master.
(Elizabeth:)Not tonight.
Tonight, you are a deliveryman.
You've brought soup but, uh-oh, Raj and I
don't have enough money to pay you.
(Elizabeth:)So we'll have to come
to some other kind of arrangement.
(Howard:)Beg pardon?
You figure out the details.
I'm gonna change into something...
(Elizabeth:)...I don't mind getting ripped off
my milky flesh.
(Howard:)What the frak?
(Raj:)Go away.
(Raj:)She wants New Delhi, not kosher deli.
(Raj:)Besides, you have a girlfriend.
(Howard:)We broke up weeks ago.